Let's take our Egyptian walk and travel with it and add our saiidi arm styling to it, all right?
Left hand facing down, right thumb by the ear.
Elbow back, weights going to shift to the right foot and lift.
Step and lift.
Good.
Switching the arms as we go make sure the hand is not moving in contrast to the hip.
The hand stays stationary.
Lift.
Step and lift.
Good.
Let's take it walking forward.
Step right foot and lift.
Step. Lift. Now feet should be together when you're doing this movement. You don't want to be stepping outside here to do the movement.
Step and then feet together.
Step feet together.
Step together.
Make sure the knee is bent.
Good step together.
Step elbow stays back.
Good so you can take this movement forward and back.
Step together.
Make sure you're not bobbing up and down and make sure you drill it in front of a mirror so that you know exactly what it looks like before you take it out into public.